A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Properties, 1923-2009; 3; 76.78 Cubic Feet 177 containers
  - Woodstock, 1948-2009; 3_12
    - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - Attendance, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Commemorative Booklet - Tenth Year - General, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Cooperative Agreements, 1997-2006 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Audit, 2003-2007 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Woodstock Inn and Resort - Budget, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program, 1999-2003 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Disney Contract, 1995 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Alexander Ilsey, Inc., 2008 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Decorating - Ahearn and Schopfer - Agreement, 2005 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Decorating - Ahearn and Schopfer - Redecorating, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Interior Design - General, 2004-2005 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Interior Design - Proposals and Approvals, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Interior Design - Alexandra Champalimaud - Proposal, 2006 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Appraisal, 1997 April 17 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      Report prepared by Crafts Appraisal Associates.
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Appraisal, 1992 July 9 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Woodstock Foundation, 1989 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Property - Woodstock and Pomfret, 1961-1987 (Box 129, Folder 1-4)
    - LSR - Property - Woodstock, 1954-1993 (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
    - LSR - Stock Agreement - Woodstock Hotel Company, 1968 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Tax Abatement Program, 1993-1997 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Surveys, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Publicity, 1992-2001 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Mansion, 2002-2004 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Aqueduct Easement, 2007 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Portfolio - Draper Fisher Jurvetson Fund V. L. P., 1999 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees and Advisory Board - Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Strategic Plan - Consultants, 2007 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board - Advisory Board, 1998-2004 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Sale of Indian Baskets, 1994-1995 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Vlaminck Painting, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - General, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Carl Taylor - Dam Property, 1992-1998 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Douglas R. Horne Land Study, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Taylor Property, 1998-2000 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - Woodstock Resort Corporation (WRC) Management Agreement, 1995-1998 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Draft Statement to New York Attorney General, 2007 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - LSR Estate - Property Appraisal - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park, 1997 April 17 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - MSKCC - Integrative Medicine Service - General, 1998-2000 (Box 139, Folder 14-15)
    - Woodstock - Corporate Files, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 16)
    - Woodstock - East End Project, 1998-2001 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Interpretive Program, 2002 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Oral History Project, 1994-1996 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Proposal, 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - LSR Fund - Grant Payment Letters, 2008 (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - General, 2006-2008 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Collections and Accreditation, 2001 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Condemnation Rights, 2000 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Corkum Property, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Exhibition Reinstallation, 2007 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Historical Narrative, 1998 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Member Survey, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Registered Trade Names, 2004 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - General, 1990-2004 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - LSR Publicity, 1997-2004 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Community Fund - General and 501c(4), 1995-2005 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Community Fund - Parking Study, 2000-2002 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Governor's Conference on Cultural Heritage Tourism, 2005-2008 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - LSR Conservation Award, 1996-1998 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - MBRNHP - Endowment Fund, 1997 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - National Geographic Proposal, 2005-2008 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Transfer of Billings Farm and Museum, 1997-1998 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - "Vermont Brand", 2007 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Writing Project - LSR Contributions to Woodstock, 2004 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock - LSR Property Planning, 1997-1999 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation (WRC) - Resort Appraisal, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock - Estate of LSR - Appraisal, 2004 (Box 149, Folder 13, Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Partnership - General, 1998-2002 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Side Letter, 1993 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Partnership - Management Issues, 1997-2000 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Memorandum of Understandings, 1997-1998 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - Mansion - Property - Transfer Documents, 1948-1993 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - LSR Letter to Roger J. Kennedy, 1994 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Forestry Agreement, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Forest Work Plan, 2000-2003 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Easements - Scenic, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Easements - Trail, 1991-2002 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - French Property, 1994-1996 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - Mansion and Contents, 1997-2004 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - Life Estate, 1998 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - Park Property, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - Scenic Easement - Blake Hill, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift - Scenic Easement - Mount Peg, 1992 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Business Health Assessment - Werner Graef Associates - General, 2005-2007 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Business Health Assessment - Werner Graef Associates - Report, 2005 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - LSR - Woodstock - Woodstock Community Fund, 2009 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - LSR Fund - General, 2001-2007 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - LSR Fund - Trust Agreement, 1994-1998 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - LSR Fund - Trustees Resolutions, 1994-2009 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - LSR Fund - Woodstock Resort Corporation Transfer, 2008 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Reports, 2002-2008 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees and Advisory Board, 2006-2007 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board - General, 1996-2008 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Archives, 2005 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Foundation - General, 2005-2009 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Public Charity Status - General, 1989-2007 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Public Charity Status - IRS Letter, 2003 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Public Charity Status - Unusual Grant Request, 2006 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Properties, 1997-2003 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Tax - Form 990, 2005-2009 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Tax - Tax Determination Letter - Public Charity, 2005 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - King Farm Addition, 2009 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - WRC Holdings - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Stock Transfer to WRC Holdings, 2008 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Budget Forecast, 2007 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Business Review and Strategic Plan, 2009 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Operating Budget, 2009 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Budgets, 2008-2009 (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Corporate Documents, 1983-2008 (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Financials, 2005-2008 (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Inn Art - Art Purchases, 1989-2002 (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Inn Art - Art Purchases, 2005-2009 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Inn Art - Reeves Contemporary, 2005-2008 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Marketing - Joint Marketing with Woodstock Foundation, 2007 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Killington Community Marketing, 2006-2008 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Operational Review, 2007 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Marketing - Planning, 2008 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Inn - Renovations - H. P. Cummings Construction Company, 2006 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Inn - Renovations - Red Rooster (Restaurant), 2008-2009 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Inn - Renovations - Red Rooster - Blue Ribbon Consulting Agreement, 2008-2009 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Cash Requirements, 2008 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Compensation Committee - Minutes, 2006 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Corporate Documents, 1989-2004 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Donath, David A., 2000-2009 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Endowment, 2005-2009 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Finance and Audit Committee Reports, 1997-2007 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Mission - Creative Economy, 2003 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Mission - General, 1998-2007 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Mission Statement, 1978-2004 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Strategic Plan, 2003-2008 (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Foundation - WRC Expenditure Responsibility Letter, 2008-2009 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Maintenance Fund - General, 1991-2009 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Maintenance Fund - Establishing Resolutions, 1992-1993 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Maintenance Fund - Guidelines and Policy, 1991-1997 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - WRC Holdings - General, 2007-2009 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - WRC Holdings - Board of Directors, 2008-2009 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - WRC Holdings - Corporate Documents, 2008 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - WRC Holdings - D & O Insurance, 2007-2008 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Management Commentaries, 2009 Fiscal, 2008-2009 (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Operating Plan 2009-2015 (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program - 2005-2010 - Timetable, 2006-2008 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program - 2005-2010 - Budgets, 2000-2007 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program - 2005-2010 - Executors' Approval, 2006 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program - 2005-2010 - Spa Planning, 2004-2009 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Improvement Program - 2005-2010 - Pool Planning, 2006 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Renovations - General, 2005-2008 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Renovations - Spa - WTS Contract, 2008 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Renovations - Spa - Cummings Construction Contract, 2008 (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Renovations - Spa - Leisure Facility Agreement (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Transfer to Woodstock Foundation, 2007 (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Woodstock - LSR Speeches - Assorted, 1969-2001 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Fundraising and Annual Appeals, 2004-2008 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Grants and Fundraising, 1996-2008 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Investment Policy, 2006 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - IRS Determination Letter re: Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1998 (Box 163, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - LSR Gold Medal, 2005 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - LSR Fund Grants, 2007-2009 (Box 163, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Woodstock Resort Corporation Cross-Marketing, 2006 (Box 163, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Foundation - NEH Grants, 2006 (Box 163, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Foundation - NEH Proposal (Exhibit Plan), 2007 (Box 163, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation: - Gary L. Avigne - General, 2005-2009 (Box 163, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Gary L. Avigne - Contracts, 2007-2009 (Box 163, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Gary L. Avigne - GM Proposal, 2008 (Box 163, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Gary L. Avigne - Pinnacle Report, 2995 (Box 163, Folder 16)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation: - Gary L. Avigne - Reports, 2006-2009 (Box 163, Folder 17)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Gary L. Avigne - IRS - Revocation of S Election, 2007 (Box 163, Folder 18)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board - Minutes, 2003-2007 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board - Executive Committee, 2006-2009 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Museum Collections, 1999-2004 (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Interior Design - Alexandra Champalimaud Associates, 2007-2008 (Box 164, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Interior Design - Peter Guzy and Asfour Guzy Architects, 2006-2008 (Box 164, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Preferred Hotel Affiliation (Box 164, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Purchase Inquiries, 2004-2007 (Box 164, Folder 15)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Rating Guidelines (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - General, 2006-2008 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - Resort Appraisals, 2004-2007 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Strategic Plan, 2007 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Tax Appeal, 1998-2005 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Tax Issues, 2009 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Transfer to Woodstock Foundation - Publicity, 2007 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Conflict of Interest Policy, 2006 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Whistleblower Policy, 2006 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Public-Private Partnerships, 2000 (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Maintenance Fund - Requests and Approvals, 2005-2009 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Gary L. Avigne - Resignation from the Board, 2009 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - General, 2006-2009 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Woodstock - Pins and Postcards, 1978-1991 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - Wyoming, 1937-2009; 3_13
    - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., 1941-2009; 3_13_1
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - General, 1993-2004 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Airport, 1990-1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Appraisal, 2001 October 8 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Minella Agreement, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Minella to Rockefeller - Closing Documents, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Boundary Adjustment - Moyer/Pierson, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Jackson Hole - Lot 18 - Surveys and Landscaping - Wirth/Jorgensten, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - LSR Estate - Wyoming - Jackson Hole - Lot 42, 2004-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - General, 1988-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - American Conservation Association (ACA), 1989-1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Beaverkill, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Board Meetings, 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 13, Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Board Minutes, 1996-2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Corporate Documents, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Financial Statements, 1993-1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - LSR Financial History - Peter Johnson, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Manitou Foundation (Douglas Horne Report), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Rungius Paintings, 1986-1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Rockefeller, Laurance S., circa 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 8)
        Copies of oral histories conducted by Ed Edwin of Columbia University's Oral History Research Office. Project funded by JHPI.
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Richards, Homer C., circa 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 9)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Struthers and Nathaniel Burt, circa 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Wirth, Conrad, circa 1966-1967 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Yokel, Michael, circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Miller, Leslie L., circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Lawrence, W. C., circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Klissold, Harry E., circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Hansen, Clifford P., circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Fabian, Harold, circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Edwin, Ed, and Jack Dornen, circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Albright, Horace M., circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - JHPI - Oral Histories - Chorley, Kenneth, circa 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated (JHPI) - Financial Statements, 2006-2007 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) - General, 1998-2009 (Box 150, Folder 1)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) - Conflict of Interest Policy, 2007 (Box 150, Folder 2)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) - Intangible Rights - Caneel Bay, St. John, 2009 (Box 150, Folder 3)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) - Trustees, 2006 (Box 150, Folder 4)
      - LSR Estate - Wyoming Probate, 2009 (Box 145, Folder 3)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - Financial Statements, 2006-2007 (Box 153, Folder 2)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - Consents and Resolutions - LSR Preserve, 2007 (Box 153, Folder 3)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - Corporate Documents, 1961-2007 (Box 153, Folder 4)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - D & O Insurance, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 5)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - Gifts - Woodstock Foundation and LSR Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 153, Folder 6)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - Grand Teton National Park - Reverter Clause (copy), 1949-1999 (Box 153, Folder 7)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - LSR Preserve Fund, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 8)
      - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JPHI) - LSR Preserve Fund - Expenditure Responsibility Letter, 2008-2009 (Box 153, Folder 9)
      - LSR Estate - Rockefeller, Mark F.: Sublease, 2008-2009 (Box 145, Folder 5)
      - LSR Fund - Corporate Documents, 1994-2005 (Box 153, Folder 10)
      - LSR Fund - Financial Reports, 2000s (Box 153, Folder 11)
      - LSR Fund - Grant to Woodstock Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 153, Folder 12)
      - LSR Fund - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) - Expenditure Responsibility Letter, 2008 (Box 153, Folder 13)
      - LSR Fund - Payments and Grants, 2009 (Box 154, Folder 1)
      - LSR Fund - Samueli Institute, 2007-2009 (Box 154, Folder 2)
      - LSR - Awards - Resolution to LSR from Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. (JHPI) and American Conversation Association (ACA), 1991 September 27 (Box 163, Folder 1)
        Presented to LSR with the Congressional Gold Medal by President George H. W. Bush.
      - JHPI - Grants-Projects Summaries, 1941-2001 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - JHPI - Grand Teton National Park - Reverter, 1994-2002 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - JHPI - Intangible Rights, 2007 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - JHPI - Intangible Rights - Caneel, St. John, 1978-2009 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - JHPI - Annual Meetings, 1986-1990 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - JHPI - Annual Meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - JHPI - Annual Meetings, 1995-1998 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - JHPI - Annual Meetings, 1999-2003 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - JHPI - 50th Anniversary Book (1940-1990) (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - LSR Preserve/JY Ranch, 1937-2008; 3_13_2
      - JY Ranch - General, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - JY Ranch - Audit - Richard Long, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - JY Ranch - Budgets (JY), 1999-2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - JY Ranch - Gift Ceremony, 2001 May 26 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - JY Ranch - Gift Ceremony - Publicity, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - JY Ranch - Historic Architectural Assessment, 2001-2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        Historic American Buildings Survey (HABS)
      - JY Ranch - Long, Richard, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)